<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>🌐RSS Available Now</title>
    <link href="/en/2024/12/19/RSS-Available-Now/"/>
    <url>/en/2024/12/19/RSS-Available-Now/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="note note-info">            <div class="h6">🌐Translated Page</div><p>This passage is translated from its <b>Simplified Chinese</b> edition. Original edition shall prevail if divergence exists.</p>          </div><p>RSS Feed funtion has been available. Readers are able to subscribe the site with RSS applications, reading the posts more conveniently.</p><h2 id="How-to-Subscribe">How to Subscribe?</h2><p>You can find the “Subscribe” button on the nav bar, which will direct you to an xml file after one click. There’s no need for you to care the chaos on the screen. What you are supposed to do is to copy the URL of the page and paste it in your RSS reader to accomplish the subscription.</p><h2 id="What-is-RSS-and-Why-Choose-It">What is RSS and Why Choose It?</h2><p>If you have no idea what is RSS, there’s a brief explanation below.</p><p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RSS">RSS</a>, which is the short for Really Simple Syndication. As its name, this technology is used for syndicating the information from websites and pushing the collection to the subscriber, so that the user can surf it in the RSS reader, instead of checking updates of every website on their own. This resembles with the “follow” function on the content and social websites that as long as you “follow” websites interested in, the updates will be automatically pushed to your syndicator; however, different from the “follow” on the content platforms, RSS has capability to fetch updates far more than one or two sources.</p><p>Reasons for choosing RSS:</p><ol><li>Saving time of checking updates manually.</li><li>Beneficial for your concentrating on really valuable information.</li><li>The categorizing function syndicators provide is helpful of sorting information sources, optimizing your info structure.</li></ol><p>Syndicators will fetch xml files from targeted links, in which the posts data are storaged. When content of websites is updated, so do the files.</p><p>RSS has several standards, among which this site employs Atom.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Announcement</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>🌐Why I Open the Blog</title>
    <link href="/en/2024/11/30/Why-I-Open-the-Blog/"/>
    <url>/en/2024/11/30/Why-I-Open-the-Blog/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="note note-info">            <div class="h6">🌐Translated Page</div><p>This passage is translated from its <b>Simplified Chinese</b> edition. Original edition shall prevail if divergence exists.</p>          </div><p><strong>Hello World!</strong></p><p>I have always wanted to document my thoughts and ideas, but for a long time, various reasons prevented me from doing so. Prolonged procrastination made me realize that many of my earlier reflections and ideas have already been lost in the desert of memory, difficult to retrieve. When I finally found a rare moment of respite to pick up the pen I had long set aside, I discovered the poverty of my knowledge and creativity. I realized that my language skills had been eroded by fragmented media, leaving me unable to effectively organize my thoughts and articulate complex feelings.</p><p>I believe the situation has become urgent. I need to continuously produce content—not fragmented, pretentious one-liners on various social media platforms, but complete and well-structured articles to document my intellectual journey. Thus, I’ve chosen this form, considered “outdated” in the modern internet landscape—a blog—to take on this task.</p><p>Unlike most blogs, this one won’t restrict its focus to computer technology. Instead, it aims to present my personal perspectives within the scope of my knowledge. While an individual’s knowledge system is inevitably limited, I sincerely invite readers to provide valuable guidance, suggestions, and critiques.</p><p>On this blog, I will share my knowledge, insights, and thoughts. I hope that through consistent updates, I can motivate myself to remain on the path of lifelong learning. This is also the reason behind the blog’s name, <em>DailyMinz</em>. If my humble efforts can offer even a small amount of help to others on their journeys, it would be deeply meaningful to me.</p><h3 id="Roadmap">Roadmap</h3><p>First, I need to address the technical issues of this blog. I’m still unfamiliar with the <a href="https://hexo.io">Hexo</a> framework and haven’t decided whether to stick with the current template. Issues like comments and multilingual support are also pressing concerns.</p><p>Second, there’s the matter of updating the blog content. But that’s not a problem—I already know what my next post will be about.</p><p>Lastly, once the blog’s content becomes more substantial, I might create dedicated sections for specific topics to help maintain updates on those subjects. I might also write things like “weekly/monthly reports” or “monthly/quarterly/annual specials,” but that’s something for later.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Announcement</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
