<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why I Open the Blog</title>
    <link href="/en/2024/11/30/Why-I-Open-the-Blog/"/>
    <url>/en/2024/11/30/Why-I-Open-the-Blog/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Hello World!</strong></p><p>I have always wanted to record my various thoughts and ideas, but for a long time, due to various reasons, I couldn’t fulfill this desire. Over time, I realized that many of my earlier reflections and ideas had been buried in the desert of memory, difficult to retrieve. When I finally had a precious moment to open my long-sealed notebook, I found myself lacking in knowledge and creativity. I also noticed how fragmented media had eroded my language skills, leaving me unable to effectively organize my thoughts and complex feelings.</p><p>It feels like the situation has become urgent. I need to continuously produce content—not fragmented, pretentious sentences on various social media platforms, but complete, well-structured articles to document my intellectual journey. That’s why I’ve chosen this “outdated” format for the internet—a blog—to take on this task.</p><p>Unlike most blogs, this one will not be confined to topics like computer technology, nor will it adhere to any fixed theme. I don’t want the journey it records to be limited to just a few fields. The brilliance of human knowledge across various domains will all be reflected in its milestones. However, because of this, it may lack the rigor I aspire to, and professional readers might even find it simplistic or laughable. Though one person’s knowledge system can hardly cover everything, I sincerely ask my readers to offer valuable guidance, suggestions, and criticisms.</p><p>On this blog, I will share my knowledge, insights, and thoughts. I hope that through continuous updates, I can push myself to remain on the path of lifelong learning. This is also why the blog is named “Daily Clarity” (每日明). I have some small ambitions as well. Once the blog has taken shape, I might create a community on GitHub to allow everyone to share their views and participate in the enrichment and improvement of this project. If this humble blog can provide even a small amount of help for someone else’s journey, it would mean the world to me.</p><h3 id="Roadmap"><a href="#Roadmap" class="headerlink" title="Roadmap"></a>Roadmap</h3><p>First, I need to address the technical issues of this blog. I’m currently unfamiliar with the Hexo framework and haven’t decided whether to stick with the current theme. There are also pressing issues like comments and multilingual support that need to be resolved.</p><p>Next comes updating the blog content. But that’s not a problem—I already know what I want to write for the next post.</p><p>Finally, once the content becomes substantial, I may create dedicated sections for certain topics to help me stay updated on those areas. I might also write things like “weekly&#x2F;monthly reports” or “monthly&#x2F;quarterly&#x2F;annual specials,” but that’s all for later.</p><p><em>This essay was generated by Google Translation. The Simplified Chinese edition prevails if conflicts exist.</em></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
